[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHARM] Toni, I'm so jealous of Billy!
Can you believe it?
Ever since college, she's had it all!
She's smart, beautiful,
and now she's getting married.
[TONI] And can you believe it?
She's marrying her first boyfriend!
- It's so perfect!
- [CHARM SIGHS HAPPILY]
What about us?
When will we have a wedding this grand?
- When?
- Soon!
- Okay.
You two should find
your Prince Charming first.
You can't have the chicken
before the egg, right?
Listen to Auntie Precious!
What about you?
Have you found your Prince Charming yet?
I don't think you've even found an egg.
- [CHUCKLING]
- Here you go. You good?
- That's her.
- Auntie!
Can I take off my barong now?
- It's so itchy.
- Not yet, sweetheart.
Your sister Billy will be here soon.
Wait, where's the groom?
Where's Alvin?
[ENGINE REVVING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here comes Billy!
[MUSIC FADES]
Excuse me.
Is Alvin on his way?
I don't know.
Uh, could you…
Could you try calling him?
We've been calling him,
but he's not answering.
- We don't know where he is.
- How's that possible?
You're his sister.
How come you don't know?
We really don't know.
[PRECIOUS] Unbelievable.
[LINE RINGING]
Bro, do you know where Alvin is?
He's not answering my calls.
What?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dude.
Is everything okay?
Hey, Annie! Come on,
call your brother already!
- [CHARM] Exactly!
- How would we know where he is?
And don't you raise your voice at me.
We don't even speak to that jerk anymore.
We were also shocked to find out that
he was getting married to some girl.
- Hold on. Let's all calm down.
- "Some girl"?
And what do you mean, "some girl"?
- Your brother's the one who isn't here!
- Exactly.
Alvin isn't coming.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sorry.
Maybe he's not here because
she really is a nobody.
- You witch!
- You too! Come here!
- You started it!
- Because it's true!
[ANNIE] Ow!
[TONI] And you call yourself a sister?
- Hey, hey, hey! Auntie Precious!
- [ARGUMENT CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
[BILLY] Get down!
Get down!
- What are you doing?
- [SLAMS]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
- Billy!
- [CAR DOOR OPENS]
[OVERLAPPING VOICES]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ARGUING INDISTINCTLY]
- Billy?!
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
Woah! Woah! Woah!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Dude, stop the car!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
I just need to talk to Alvin.
I know that's not all
you're planning to do, Billy.
I know you.
Oh, so you do know.
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
Oh!
- [INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- Billy, someone's there!
- [CAR HORN BLARING]
- [JORDAN] Oh, shit!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [HORNS BLARING]
- [INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh my God!
- [GIA] Hurry up, Alvin!
- [ALVIN] All right, all right!
- [SCREAMS]
- [ALVIN] Hey!
- Hey! Oh my-- Wait.
- Wait. Why didn't you close it?
We almost killed someone!
Dude.
Just stop.
You shouldn't be doing this.
Dude! Hello?
We're going to crash.
We're going to crash
if you don't stay quiet!
Do you want to die, huh?
I want someone else dead, not me.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[ALVIN] I'm almost done. Let's go.
[MUSIC TURNS MOROSE]
Oh no.
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
What are you planning to do?
[GIA WHIMPERS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE SPUTTERS]
- It won't start.
- For crying out loud!
[CAR ENGINE ROARING]
- We need to go down.
- Huh?
- Get out.
- [ENGINE ROARS]
I said get out!
- [WHIMPERS] Get out?
- Let's go!
What?!
- Vin, it won't come off.
- What do you mean?!
- Just try! Why did it have to break now?!
- [GIA] Vin!
This isn't funny.
- It won't come off. It's broken!
- All right, all right. I'll do it!
[CAR ENGINE ROARS]
[JORDAN] Billy, stop it.
Billy, that's not funny.
[CAR ENGINE ROARS]
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
- Billy!
Billy? Billy!
- Don't interfere!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Dude! No!
- Jordan!
Billy!
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
The thing I hate most
is a cheater.
But you still became one.
Why?
Why?!
Billy.
It's not worth it.
Let's just go.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- [GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
[LAUGHS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BILLY] Wait a minute.
Just wait a minute.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC TURNS SOMBER]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you okay?
Mm-hmm. Of course I am.
- It's okay to cry.
- Are you okay?
Hey, you can cry!
I already cried once because of a man.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
That'll be the last one.
[BILLY] It's all right!
Let's just have fun.
[YOUNG BILLY] Please don't leave us, Dad!
[CRYING] Please don't leave.
Please!
[KEEPS SOBBING]
[YOUNG BILLY] Mommy, please--
Don't waste your tears on worthless men.
[OLIVE] We don't need him.
We can live without him.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CRYING]
[PRECIOUS HALF-SOBS]
Why are you crying, Auntie Pres?
Were you the one who got left behind?
- I don't know why either.
- You're crying a lot.
That's enough.
Are you the bride?
Put on your veil.
[CRYING, CHUCKLING]
[BILLY] It's okay. Let's just have fun.
It's all right.
Go ahead, Auntie Pres.
I'll join you later.
Okay.
- [PRECIOUS CHUCKLES FAINTLY]
- [BILLY] Mm! Mm!
Auntie Pres, that's enough.
No more tears.
[PRECIOUS] Fine, all right.
- My dude.
- Mm-hmm?
May I have this dance?
- [IN BRITISH ACCENT] Of course.
- Of course.
[GIGGLES]
["KULIMLIM" BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
When are you returning to Australia?
Tomorrow.
We'll have our midterm exams.
Don't waste your scholarship.
Exactly.
It's my last year.
Sorry you wasted your airfare.
It's not a waste.
What are you even saying?
I'm glad I went home.
If I'm not here,
who's gonna be by your side?
["KULIMLIM" CONTINUES]
Hey, you know
I'm always here for you, right?
As you should be.
And…
he's an idiot.
Alvin's really a jerk.
He's a huge jerk.
- Really.
And, to be honest,
you weren't a good match.
Why are you just telling me this now?
Would you have listened?
Do you ever listen to me?
["KULIMLIM" CONTINUES]
Thank you.
I got you.
["KULIMLIM" CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
You crashed into my car!
- You just suddenly turned!
- Huh?
Do you even know how to drive?
Look at what you did!
[MAN 1] You suddenly cut me off!
- I was doing fine.
- [MAN 2] Why didn't you move?
Look, I was in the right lane!
- I was on my way!
- Look at the damage you caused!
[MAN 1] Yes, that's your fault!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOTORCYCLE APPROACHING]
- Oop, oop! Okay.
- Good afternoon, ma'am!
Good afternoon!
Thank you so much!
Here you go.
- Thank you, ma'am!
- Take care on your way home.
Will do, thanks.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir, it's 5:00 p.m. already!
Our guests are arriving by 5:30!
The LED and stage setup have
been delayed by two hours.
What's the plan now?
"What's the plan?" You're so stubborn!
What do you want me to do, huh?
I already said it got stuck in traffic!
It's also Friday today.
But if…
you give me your number,
I'll make them hurry for you.
Pervert!
If my boss comes here
and the setup's still not done,
I'm telling you, you're doomed!
[AUDIO MAN] Why would I care
about your boss, huh?
Who even is she?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm just the person paying you.
And I won't pay you if you don't finish
the stage setup in 30 minutes.
And why are you talking
to my staff like that?
Is that how a man should talk to women?
You're even married.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
And you have a child too.
S-sorry, ma'am.
How dare you hit on my staff?
I don't think you're setting
a good example for your child.
If you ever do this again,
I'll have you arrested.
And I'm going to tell your wife myself.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, ma'am. I'm sorry.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You okay?
- Thank you, chief.
- Okay.
[WOMAN] I'm done with players.
I want someone loyal
who will stick to one.
Someone who can support my goals
and celebrate me for my career.
Love it!
Instead of hurting me,
they should be protecting me.
- That's right!
- Exactly!
A man who doesn't put himself first.
What made us believe in forever?
- LoveList!
[FEMALE VOICE OVER]
With the top-rated dating app
now in its second year,
finding your forever is easier than ever.
First, download LoveList.
Sign up.
Verify.
Done.
Second, build your profile.
If you're a searcher,
just create your LoveList.
Make a list of all the qualities
you want in a partner.
If you're a pursuer,
just make a checklist
of your lifestyle, hobbies,
personality traits,
whatever makes you, you.
Then our smart-matching feature
will do the rest.
We will provide you
with your perfect match.
Need backup?
Go to LoveSpeak,
a safe space for searchers
to connect, talk, and get opinions
from your fellow LoveListers.
Join LoveList,
and find the right love at the right time.
[HOST] Let us all welcome
the CEO of LoveList,
Ms. Billy Cariño!
[APPLAUSE, CHEERS]
Thank you.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Yes, it's true.
Love gives second chances
to those who deserve it.
And these women are proof of that.
[APPLAUSE]
Thank you.
I believe that
love should only
be given to the right person.
And yes, there are still a lot
of good people out there.
That's why LoveList,
a matchmaking and dating app,
is here for you.
But we created not just an application,
but a community of women who work together
to help you find "the one."
Because I believe
that love is supposed to be
the most beautiful thing
that can happen to you.
As long as it is with the right one.
[IN UNISON] At the right time!
[APPLAUSE, CHEERS]
[BILLY] So, ladies and gentlemen,
let me introduce you to the women
who made all of this possible.
My LoveList family.
- Whoo!
- [CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
Our design and marketing head,
and one of my college besties,
the beautiful Ms. Charm Torres.
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
[RALPH] Go, baby!
[BILLY] And my other bestie,
our CFO,
and the one who brings
good luck and good vibes,
Ms. Toni Prieto.
- [CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
- [MOUTHS INAUDIBLY]
[BILLY] And the newest member of our team,
she is our influencer girly
slash our social media manager.
Let us all welcome Marj Quinto!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
And fun fact,
Toni and Charm were the first users
of the LoveList app.
And just like you,
this is where they found their forever.
- Yes! We did!
- [APPLAUSE]
And because we are celebrating
our second anniversary,
we are preparing something
bigger and better for LoveList.
And I'm sure that here, love is better,
whether it's the
first or second time around,
as long as you're with the right one…
- At the right time!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
Yeah!
- Congratulations! LoveList!
- [BILL] Aw…
[CHEERING]
- [BILLY] Thank you.
- [CROWD SHOUTS SUPPORTIVELY]
[CAMERAS CLICKING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Given that you're the CEO of LoveList,
I'm sure you must have
an exciting love life.
I'm so sorry I'm late!
- You made it!
- I made it.
Is he your boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
No! No, no.
- He's my childhood best friend.
- That's right.
We were also classmates
from elementary to high school.
So, girls, meet Jordan Valentin.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi!
Yes. He is the head of our IT department.
And he's the one
who helped develop the app.
[MARIZ] Wow!
So you're a tech genius?
- Not really.
- Yes, you are.
He also earned his degree
in Computer Science in Australia,
on a full scholarship.
- Thanks for the intro.
- Mm-hmm. You're welcome.
And I'm also a full-time bar owner.
If you need a bar or even a mobile bar
for parties, events,
or just a good time, here you go.
- It's called Jade & Jude's.
- Thank you.
For real? I thought you also
met him through the app.
[GIGGLING]
Oh, I don't meet her standards.
- Do you know why?
- Why?
Because what you're looking for
is Mr. Perfect.
- No. I am open to dating.
- Impossible standards.
But it takes a while
to find the one, right?
It's okay. I'm not in a hurry.
He'll come.
- At the right time!
Exactly.
- Cheers!
- Congrats, by the way.
- [GLASSES CLINK]
- Thank you.
- You deserve it.
- Mm-hmm.
- Babe.
- Oh.
Girls, this is Valerie.
- Hi!
- Hello!
I actually know Valerie.
I've been a fan of yours since day one.
No wonder Jordan looks familiar to me.
- Mm…
- Did you meet on LoveList?
Not really. [CHUCKLES]
Actually, we're products of destiny.
- [OOHING]
- Yeah. [CHUCKLES]
We got together during
our freshman year in Australia.
- We lasted… five months?
- Five months.
Five months, yeah.
But I had to go back to the Philippines,
so we broke up.
But last year, we met at a party,
and we hit it off. [GIGGLES]
See? Destiny. [GIGGLES]
[CAR APPROACHING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYS RATTLING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[YAWNS]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
- It's past your bedtime. Go to bed.
It's past ten o'clock! You said
you'd go to sleep five minutes ago.
[OLIVER] Hold on, Auntie.
I'm still fixing this font downloader
that you clicked on earlier.
A virus managed to get through.
It was a close one!
I didn't know. I thought it was free.
Exactly. It says "Free Font Download,"
but when you install it,
it comes with a Trojan.
What's a Trojan?
It's a virus, Auntie Pres.
- He's talking about a virus.
- Oh. [CHUCKLES]
- Hello, I'm home.
- You're here!
- What is that?
- I don't even know!
- [SMOOCHES]
- What's that?
My PC got a virus because of Auntie.
It's a good thing
I detected it right away.
It was all my fault. I'm sorry.
Hey, Billy, congratulations!
- Your event was a success.
- Thank you.
I saw the coverage of it online.
You should go to bed. I know you're tired.
I also need to go to the center now.
Some kids from Pampanga
are arriving later.
- I need to welcome them.
- [BILLY] Sure.
But, I cooked your favorite!
Sinigang. So, just eat that.
- Thank you!
- But you need to go to bed!
- Thank you, Auntie Pres.
- Go to bed, okay? [SMOOCHES]
- Bye!
- Love you! [SMOOCHES]
- Love you! Take care of everything, okay?
- Yes, I can take it from here.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Can I ask Bro Dude
to download a new antivirus?
Well… It's late.
And Jordan is probably tired.
We can ask him tomorrow.
- Okay?
- Okay, tomorrow.
And can we turn that off
after five minutes?
Okay, after five minutes.
And maybe we can replace your patch?
[OLIVER] I can do that on my own later.
- Hmm.
- I promise.
- Hmm. Okay.
You have five minutes, okay?
- Okay.
- Good night!
- Good night. Love you.
- Love you.
- Good night.
[VALERIE] Guys, this is my baby.
Say hi to my Valerieverse fam!
I WISH I HAD THAT TOO
Hi, Valerieverse fam. We'll eat first.
Babe!
What are you doing?
I was just about to peak in views!
[JORDAN] Babe.
Can we have a little alone time?
You know I don't want our relationship
to be everyone's business.
But this is what makes me happy.
But they weren't there when we started.
But this is who I am now.
Just a little bit of privacy, babe.
That's all I'm asking for.
[SIGHS]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, fine.
But don't get mad at me anymore.
[SIGHS]
That won't work again.
Please smile for me.
- C'mon! Just give me a smile!
- Stop.
Just give me a smile so I know
that we've made up.
Come on. Let's eat.
C'mon, just a smile?
Or maybe you want a kiss instead.
Please? [SMOOCHES]
Fine!
- I'm smiling. Let's eat, c'mon.
- Okay.
[THUNDER ROARS]
[HEAVY THUD]
Oliver?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDER ROARS]
Oliver.
Oliver?
Oliver? I'm here!
Can you hear me, Oliver?
- [BREATHING SHAKILY]
- [THUNDER ROARS]
Oliver?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wake up!
Oliver!
[CRYING] Oliver!
We're going to the hospital, okay?
Don't close your eyes, Oliver.
Oliver?
Oliver!
Can you hear me?
Just hold on, okay? We're almost there.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR ENGINE HUMS]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [THUDS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma'am, stay here.
[WOMAN GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS IN PAIN]
[YOUNG BILLY PANTING]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Take good care of your brother.
M-Ma, why are you saying that?
You're smart.
You're a bright kid.
You're brave.
Ma, I'm not brave.
- Ma…
- You'll get through this.
[SOBS] Ma, I can't!
Don't leave me, Ma.
- [OLIVE GROANING]
- [YOUNG BILLY SOBBING]
[YOUNG BILLY SNIFFLES, SOBS] Ma…
- Ma!
- You're not allowed here, dear.
Ma!
- [DOCTOR] Ma'am?
- [YOUNG BILLY WAILING] Ma!
- [DOCTOR] Time of death…
- Ma!
Mama!
- Ma! Please! Ma!
- [DOCTOR] Time of death, 2:05.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[YOUNG BILLY WAILING] Ma!
Where's your dad, dear?
He's gone.
My father is dead.
[BABY CRYING]
Doc, let's administer…
Okay.
Can you move your toes, Oliver?
[VOICE BREAKING] Okay.
Okay.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[SNIFFLES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUFFLED SOBS]
[SNIFFLES]
[SIGHS]
[MUSIC TURNS GENTLE]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[YOUNG BILLY SOBBING]
[BABY COOING]
Why are you alone?
Where's your mom?
My mother just died.
My father left us.
We have no relatives.
[YOUNG BILLY SOBS]
It's just my baby brother and me.
[YOUNG JORDAN] We're the same then.
[SNIFFLES]
Mommy just died.
Dad left us with Grandpa.
My name is Jordan.
Billy.
[BOTH SNIFFLING, SOBBING]
I don't know what to do.
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
There are people who want to take us.
They'll separate my brother and me.
[SNIFFLES]
I don't want that.
I won't let them do that.
[YOUNG BILLY CRYING]
I won't.
No way!
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [MUSIC FADES]
Diabetes is really a traitor,
especially at Oliver's age.
He's going through puberty
and his body is experiencing
hormonal changes.
His patch should be replaced
as much as possible.
Hmm, you heard that?
If it's time to change your patch,
you can't say,
"Give me five minutes," hmm?
I'm sorry, Billy.
I'm sorry, Doc.
I've told you everything
you should take note of.
- You know what to do.
- Yes.
- Yes. Doc, thank you so much.
- Okay?
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Doc.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Hmm…
- Heard that?
- Naughty.
- Good morning, Ms. Billy.
- Hello.
This is the new prescription
for Oliver's adjusted doses.
Okay.
Oh, ma'am! Aren't you the CEO of LoveList?
Oh!
Here.
I've matched with someone
who's my type this month.
- Ooh.
- At first,
I wasn't sure if I'd go on with it.
Luckily, LoveList has a special feature.
[LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
LoveSpeak.
Exactly, ma'am. LoveSpeak.
I got to know Bryan better.
I was convinced by LoveList's
community's comments,
so yeah, we'll have our fifth date later.
- Wow.
- Wow! [CLAPS]
Congrats.
Happy for you.
Thank you, ma'am, sir.
If you need anything for your son,
just look for me.
I will assist you and Daddy.
Oh, no. He's not the daddy.
- No, no, no.
- Me?
- Oliver is Billy's brother.
- Hey, son.
So, he's not the daddy.
He's her best friend.
- Right?
- He's adopted.
That nurse was ridiculous.
I stayed up late for just one night,
but I already look like a mother?
Ah! It seems true.
- Is that so?
- Right?
- Don't forget-- Thank you, sir.
- Anytime, ma'am.
She also mistook you for Oliver's father!
- Yes, Daddy?
- Door.
Well, someday, I will become a father.
- Be careful.
- [GUARD] All right.
- Thank you! Here.
- [GUARD] Take care.
- Thank you.
- What do you mean, you'll become a father?
Are you ready for that?
Have you even proposed to Valerie?
- Propose?
- Yes!
- Not yet, Auntie Pres.
- [PRECIOUS] Mm-hmm.
[JORDAN] I'm not yet ready.
But, of course, someday, I'd like to.
I want to have my own family.
But first, there have to be
more branches of the bar.
Of course, there's Grandpa.
I want to upgrade his facilities.
- Mm-hmm.
- I need to save.
- That's right. That's right.
- I want to make music-- Wait.
Why me? Billy should get a family first.
- Me? Shouldn't it be Auntie Pres first?
- [PRECIOUS] He's right.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you so much
for that wonderful question.
I believe I don't need a man.
- No offense, okay?
- Ouch.
Lots of people at
Angels of Grace already love me.
And you're here too,
so I'm okay. I'm fine.
Wow!
Thank you so much for that wonderful
answer, candidate number 1.
Well? Are you coming with us?
- No, it's out of the way.
- Okay.
I'll just take a taxi,
so this naughty kid can rest.
[BILLY] Mm!
- All right, all right, okay.
- All right.
Thank you,
and sorry for the inconvenience.
- It's fine.
- I thought I'd be late.
Take care.
Thank you. I'll make it up to you.
I'm free anytime so long as it's you.
- I'm good with three bottles.
- That's it?
[CHUCKLING]
How's Oliver? Is he okay?
[BILLY] Oh, yes! He's okay now. Thank you.
[JORDAN] Val!
Why'd you come here?
This is a long way from your condo.
Just because!
I saw your message this morning.
I was going to jog around the oval,
and that's near here,
so I thought of coming by.
Thanks, babe.
Billy!
- Be careful driving, okay?
- [BILLY] Yes, thank you. Bye!
- [JORDAN] Wear your seat belt.
- [BILLY] Yes. Bye.
[JORDAN] Auntie Pres.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
["SUGAL" BY BRYAN CHONG PLAYING]
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
Thank you.
["SUGAL" CONTINUES]
[ROBBIE] Who's Bryan Chong?
He has a nice voice!
I heard him sing at a party.
He's from Cebu.
He doesn't know anyone here,
so I want to help him.
I mean, he's great!
["SUGAL" CONTINUES]
Waiter!
Quick.
Yes, sir?
There's a strand of hair in your sisig.
I'm sorry, but we wear hairnets
in the kitchen.
Hey! Are you calling me a liar?
[JORDAN] Sir! Just wait a minute.
Please don't disrespect our staff.
Hah. So I'm the disrespectful one here?
Fine. I won't make a fuss
if you put my food on the house.
And give me a new plate of sisig.
Wait a minute.
You ordered a lot! You're scamming us!
You're crazy.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Rain!
- [CUSTOMER GRUNTS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [CUSTOMER GROANING]
You really don't want to stop?
- [CHAIR THUDS]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[CUSTOMER GROANING]
We got you! But where did you get this?
You don't even have hair on your head.
Robbie, call the police.
- [JORDAN] You okay?
- [RAIN] It hurts, boss.
[ROBBIE CHUCKLING]
- That was a bit wild.
- Well, he was big, boss!
- I know.
- Right? Did you see his body?
I even hit him with a chair.
- He didn't stop.
And then he wanted to punch me again!
Yeah, I did see him going closer to you.
Good thing the boss arrived.
While you were
just standing there earlier.
Yeah.
- What did you do?
- Because I knew!
- I knew you could handle him.
- Oh, wow.
I conceded because
I knew you could handle him.
Right?
Listen.
Our sales are still good,
although we're a mess.
That's true.
[VALERIE BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [ROBBIE] This one?
- Hi, babe.
- Hi, Jordan!
I just finished working out.
- Want to grab a midnight snack?
- Sorry, Val.
We're not done at the bar yet.
We still have to check the inventory.
Tomorrow, I promise.
I'll make it up to you.
Okay, fine.
Are you mad?
No. No, I'm fine.
Anyway, I have to go now. Bye-bye.
- [SIGHING DEEPLY]
- [GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[PHONE THUDS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN DISTANCE]
[BILLY] Yes, Auntie Pres. I just arrived.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Ms. Billy.
Is Oliver's new glucose dosage
in the fridge?
The one I prepared?
Yes, I saw it.
Please also check his
sugar level before bedtime,
or if he looks weak.
If the low alarm goes off…
- Good morning, ma'am!
- Morning.
…that means he needs to eat,
even if it's just borderline.
- Good morning, chief!
- Good morning.
E-signature, please.
Oh, you'll do it upstairs.
But talk to this baby boy.
He's been bugging me for a while now.
Oliver.
Yes, I told Auntie that
you'll be staying there.
Don't be stubborn.
But, Billy, we have an exam today!
I already emailed your teacher earlier.
You'll be given a make-up exam.
Didn't the doctor say you need to rest?
Don't be difficult, come on.
When you return to school,
you'll be given a glucagon kit.
I already taught your teacher
how to use it.
So during PE or any sports activity…?
The insulin dose should be reduced,
and carbs increased.
I already know that, Billy.
So when will I be going back to school?
Tomorrow? The next day?
Ssh. Shh, look at you.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
He's so stubborn, right?
Don't think about it.
It's better than forcing him
to go to school, right?
Don't worry. I'm on leave until next week.
I'll take care of him.
N-Next week?!
So that means I won't be going
to school until next week?
Biboy might end up
being the top of the class!
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, see? He takes after someone I know!
Hmph! Anyway, bye-bye.
All right, Auntie Pres.
You're in charge of him.
Thank you. Bye, Oliver!
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[BILLY] LoveList knows that
love can get complicated.
So after LoveSpeak, here comes LoveLine.
Heartbroken? Confused?
On LoveLine, you can talk
to real professionals
who are always ready to guide
and listen to you.
Real people.
Real advice.
Real love.
What do you guys think?
I feel like
we need to visualize LoveLine more.
Like, what it is. What it comes with.
Ah, do we have sample clips of our booths?
Even rough ideas?
Do you have any?
We can ask Jordan to build an AI model.
Yes.
While waiting for LoveLine's
official launch, uh…
we'll sustain teasers
on LoveList's socials.
Mm-hmm.
Billy, the cost of this rollout
is no joke.
I'm already wearing these
wealth crystals every day.
I don't even know where
to get the budget anymore.
Yes, I know.
Don't worry, I'll have a meeting
with a possible investor on Friday.
What if…
- No deal?
- Yeah.
Well, I studied their company carefully.
We seem to share the same core values.
It looks like we're aligned
with their mission and vision.
So, I think there will be a deal.
I think. Let's claim it.
Miss, they're currently
in the middle of a meeting!
Chief, I couldn't stop her.
Billy, can we talk?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
In private?
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN DISTANCE]
Ever since Jordan and I started dating,
I've been helping you promote
LoveList for 11 months now.
For free.
So, it's my turn to ask for a favor.
Of course.
What do you need from me?
[SIGHS]
[MUSIC BUILDING UP]
I want to propose to Jordan,
and you're gonna help me set it up.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, wow.
Are you sure?
I mean--
Have you really thought this through?
Didn't you just celebrate
your first anniversary?
I think that's enough time for me
to realize that
we're meant to be together.
For good.
[BILLY] Oh.
I want him.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I finally found my Prince Charming!
I felt it wasn't my place to stop Val.
[JORDAN] It's been years.
There's still no update
about my mom's case.
[JUDE] Who are you?
[NURSE] I hope you never get tired of
taking care of your grandpa.
Through this, you'll be able
to express yourself freely.
Why are you painting a bird?
[ABI] Because I want to be free.
My father left us.
So did my sibling.
[BILLY] I just feel like
someone's watching me.